A Guide to the Asia Society Exhibition files FA258
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ancient Art from Afghanistan, Exhibited: 1966 January-March
  The Exhibition, subtitled "Treasures of the Kabul Museum", was presented under the patronage of His Majesty, Mohammed Zaher Shah, King of Afghanistan. Objects for the Exhibition were selected by Benjamin Rowland, Jr., Gleason Professor of Fine Arts, Harvard University, Cambridge, Massachusetts. Dr. Rowland also wrote the catalogue for the Exhibition. After its showing at Asia House, the Exhibition was subsequently displayed in the Lytton Gallery of the Los Angeles County Museum of Art, Los Angeles, California, and at the National Collection of Fine Arts, Smithsonian Institution, Washington, D.C.
  - Acoustiguide Script, undated (Box 26, Folder 235)
  - Background Material, 1963, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 236)
  - Breakages, 1965-1966 (Box 26, Folder 237)
  - Breakages: Record of Treatment, undated (Box 26, Folder 238)
  - Catalogue: Annotated, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 239)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence A-Z, 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 240)
  - Catalogue: "Exhibition of Ancient Art of Afghanistan", Japan, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 241)
  - Catalogue: "L'Afghanistan Dalla Preistoria All'Islam", Galleria Civica D'Arte Moderna - Torina, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 242)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Original, undated (Box 27, Folder 243)
  - Catalogue: Map - Negative and Positive, undated (Box 27, Folder 244)
  - Catalogue: Proof, First, undated (Box 27, Folder 245)
  - Catalogue: Proof, Rowland Corrections, undated (Box 27, Folder 246)
  - Catalogue: Proof, Second, undated (Box 28, Folder 247)
  - Correspondence A-L, 1961, 1963-1966, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 248)
  - Correspondence M-Z, 1961-1966 (Box 28, Folder 249)
  - Correspondence: Kabul Museum, 1961, 1963-1968 (Box 28, Folder 250)
  - Correspondence: Benjamin Rowland, Jr., 1963-1968 (Box 28, Folder 251)
  - Daily Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 28, Folder 252)
  - Dinner Parties - Pre-preview, 1965-1966 (Box 29, Folder 253)
  - Guest Pages, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 254)
  - Installation, 1965-1967 (Box 29, Folder 255)
  - Installation: Photos, Color and Duplicates, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 256)
  - Lectures, 1965-1966 (Box 29, Folder 257)
  - Loan Agreement and Insurance, 1965-1967 (Box 29, Folder 258)
  - Opening: Preview, 1965-1966 (Box 29, Folder 259)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1965-1966 (Box 29, Folder 260)
  - Photos, Musée Guimet Pictures, undated (Box 30, Folder 261)
  - Photos: Pictures and Negatives Not in Show, undated (Box 30, Folder 262)
  - Photos: J. Powell, undated (Box 30, Folder 263)
  - Publicity, 1964-1967 (Box 30, Folder 264)
  - Slides and Permission, 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 265)
  - Travel of Exhibition - Los Angeles, 1963-1966 (Box 30, Folder 266)
  - Travel of Exhibition - Washington, D.C., 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 267)
  - U.S. Travel - Mohammad Karim Barakzai and Ahmad Ali Motamedi, 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 268)
- 7000 Years of Iranian Art, Exhibited: 1966 May-June
  The Exhibition titled "7000 Years of Iranian Art" was originally organized and circulated in 1964-1965 by the Smithsonian Institution, Washington, D.C. At the conclusion of its American tour, the Exhibition, reduced in size to fit the limited spaces of Asia House, was displayed by the Asia Society.
  - Acoustiguide Script, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 269)
  - Catalogue, 1964-1966 (Box 30, Folder 270)
  - Checklist: Asia House Exhibition, 1964-1966 (Box 31, Folder 271)
  - Chronology, undated (Box 31, Folder 272)
  - Correspondence A-Z, 1964-1966 (Box 31, Folder 273)
  - Daily Reports, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 274)
  - Extension of Exhibition, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 275)
  - Guest Book, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 276)
  - Installation, 1965-1966 (Box 31, Folder 277)
  - Loan Agreements, 1965-1966 (Box 31, Folder 278)
  - Opening, 1965-1966 (Box 31, Folder 279)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1965-1966 (Box 32, Folder 280)
  - Photos: Not in Exhibit, undated (Box 32, Folder 281)
  - Publicity, 1964-1966 (Box 32, Folder 282)
  - Suggested Bibliography, undated (Box 32, Folder 283)
- Master Bronzes of India, Exhibited: 1966 October-December
  The Exhibition of approximately 60 bronzes was reassembled from an exhibition previously shown at museums in Cleveland, Ohio, Chicago, Illinois, and Kansas City, Missouri. The catalogue for the Exhibition was published by The Art Institute of Chicago.
  - Acoustiguide Script, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 284)
  - Catalogue, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 285)
  - Catalogue: Annotated, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 286)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1966, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 287)
  - Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 32, Folder 288)
  - Daily Reports, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 289)
  - Guest Book, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 290)
  - Installation, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 291)
  - Loan Agreements, 1965-1966 (Box 33, Folder 292)
  - Opening, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 293)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 294)
  - Publicity, 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 295)
  - Slide Permission Letters, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 296)
- Chinese Art from the Collection of H. M. King Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden, Exhibited: 1967 January-February
  The Exhibition was assembled by Bo Gyllensvärd in cooperation with John Alexander Pope for a tour of American museums organized by the International Exhibitions Foundation, Washington, D.C. Mr. Gyllensvärd, Keeper of the King's Chinese Collection and Director of the Museum of Far Eastern Antiquities, Stockholm, Sweden, and Dr. Pope, Director of the Freer Gallery of Art, Smithsonian Institution, Washington, D.C., authored the catelogue for the Exhibition.
  - Acoustiguide, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 297)
  - Catalogue, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 298)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1965-1967 (Box 34, Folder 299)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements: Bo Gyllensvärd, 1965-1967 (Box 34, Folder 300)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements: Annemarie H. Pope, 1965-1967 (Box 34, Folder 301)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 34, Folder 302)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, undated (Box 34, Folder 303)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Original, undated (Box 34, Folder 304)
  - Guest Book, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 308)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, undated (Box 34, Folder 305)
  - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 34, Folder 306)
  - Daily Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 35, Folder 307)
  - Installation, 1966-1967 (Box 35, Folder 309)
  - Lectures, 1966-1967 (Box 35, Folder 310)
  - Loan Agreement, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 311)
  - Openings, 1965-1967 (Box 35, Folder 312)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1966-1967 (Box 35, Folder 313)
  - Publicity, 1966-1968 (Box 35, Folder 314)
- Fantastics and Eccentrics in Chinese Painting, Exhibited: 1967 March-May
  The Exhibition, selected by James Cahill, Professor of Oriental Art, University of California, Berkeley, was shown at Asia House in the spring of 1967. It was subsequently exhibited at the Los Angeles County Museum of Art in California and at the M. H. de Young Memorial Museum, San Francisco, California. Dr. Cahill wrote the catalogue for the Exhibition.
  - Acoustiguide Script, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 315)
  - Catalogue: Annotated, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 316)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 36, Folder 317)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Original, undated (Box 36, Folder 318)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Typed, undated (Box 36, Folder 319)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript and Proofs, 1966-1967 (Box 36, Folder 320)
  - Condition Reports, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 321)
  - Correspondence, 1962, 1964-1969 (Box 36, Folder 322)
  - Correspondence: James Cahill, 1962-1967 (Box 36, Folder 323)
  - Daily Reports, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 324)
  - Guest Book, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 325)
  - Installation, 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 326)
  - Lectures, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 327)
  - Loan Agreements and Correspondence: A-L, 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 328)
  - Loan Agreements and Correspondence: M-Z, 1966-1968 (Box 37, Folder 329)
  - Opening, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 330)
  - Packing and Shipping, Insurance, Import License, 1967-1968 (Box 38, Folder 331)
  - Photos: Poor Prints, undated (Box 38, Folder 332)
  - Photos: Section VII Objects, undated (Box 38, Folder 333)
  - Publicity, 1957, 1963, 1966-1968 (Box 38, Folder 334)
  - Refusals and Withdrawals, 1966-1967 (Box 38, Folder 335)
  - Slide Permission Letters, 1967, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 336)
  - Symposium, 1966-1967 (Box 38, Folder 337)
  - Travel of Exhibition: Los Angeles, 1966-1967, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 338)
  - Travel of Exhibition: San Francisco, 1966-1967 (Box 38, Folder 339)
- Japanese Arts of the Heian Period: 794-1185, Exhibited: 1967 October-December
  The objects in the Exhbition were selected by John Rosenfield, Associate Professor, Department of Fine Arts, Harvard University, Cambridge, Massachusetts. Dr. Rosenfield also authored the catalogue. The Exhibition was subsequently shown at Harvard University's Fogg Art Museum.
  - Acoustiguide Script, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 340)
  - Catalogue: Annotated, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 341)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 39, Folder 342)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence: Keating Weatherhill, 1966-1967 (Box 39, Folder 343)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, undated (Box 39, Folder 344)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript (1), undated (Box 39, Folder 345)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript (2), undated (Box 39, Folder 346)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Original (1), undated (Box 40, Folder 347)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Original (2), undated (Box 40, Folder 348)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, John Rosenfield, undated (Box 40, Folder 349)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Typed Copies, undated (Box 40, Folder 350)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, Corrected, undated (Box 40, Folder 351)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, Corrected: Photographs (1), undated (Box 41, Folder 352)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, Corrected: Photographs (2), undated (Box 41, Folder 353)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, Uncorrected, undated (Box 41, Folder 354)
  - Condition Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 41, Folder 355)
  - Correspondence: Domestic, 1965-1968 (Box 41, Folder 356)
  - Correspondence: Foreign, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 357)
  - Correspondence: Morgan-Manhattan-Allied Van Lines, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 358)
  - Correspondence: John Rosenfield, 1964-1968 (Box 41, Folder 359)
  - Correspondence: Lila Acheson Wallace, 1966-1968 (Box 41, Folder 360)
  - Curator, 1967-1968 (Box 41, Folder 361)
  - Daily Reports, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 362)
  - Guest Book, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 363)
  - Installation, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 364)
  - Lectures, 1966-1968 (Box 42, Folder 365)
  - Loan Agreements, A-F, 1966-1968 (Box 42, Folder 366)
  - Loan Agreements, G-I, 1966-1968 (Box 42, Folder 367)
  - Loan Agreements, J-P, 1966-1968 (Box 42, Folder 368)
  - Loan Agreements, Q-Z, 1966-1968 (Box 43, Folder 369)
  - Opening, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 370)
  - Packing, Shipping, Insurance, 1964, 1966-1968 (Box 43, Folder 371)
  - Photos: Inferior, undated (Box 43, Folder 372)
  - Photos: Objects Not in Exhibit, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 373)
  - Publicity, 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folder 374)
  - Slide Permission Letters, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 375)
  - Travel of Exhibition: Fogg Museum, 1965-1968 (Box 43, Folder 376)
- Chinese Treasures from the Avery Brundage Collection, Exhibited: 1968 January-March
  The objects in the Exhibition were selected from the Avery Brundage Collection by René-Yvon Lefebvre d’Argencé, Director of the Avery Brundage Foundation. Following its showing at Asia House, the Exhibition traveled to museums in Detroit, Michigan; Chicago, Illinois; Honolulu, Hawaii; Seattle, Washington; Portland, Oregon; and San Francisco, California. The catalogue for the Exhibition was authored by Mr. d’Argencé.
  - Acoustiguide Script, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 377)
  - Catalogue: Annotated File Copy, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 378)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1967-1969 (Box 44, Folder 379)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 380)
  - Catalogue: Japanese Language Edition, 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 381)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, undated (Box 44, Folder 382)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Edited: File Copy, undated (Box 44, Folder 383)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Original, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 384)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript Information, undated (Box 44, Folder 385)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 386)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 45, Folder 387)
  - Correspondence: René-Yvon Lefebvre d’Argencé, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 388)
  - Daily Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 389)
  - Dinner, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 390)
  - Guest Book, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 391)
  - Installation, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 392)
  - Lecture, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 393)
  - Loan Agreement, 1967-1969 (Box 45, Folder 394)
  - Opening, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 395)
  - Packing, Shipping, Insurance, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 396)
  - Photos: Inferior, undated (Box 46, Folder 397)
  - Publicity, 1966-1969 (Box 46, Folder 398)
  - Slides, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 399)
- The Art of the Korean Potter, Exhibited: 1968 April-June
  The objects in the Exhibition were selected by Robert P. Griffing, Jr., Curatorial Consultant, Honolulu Academy of Arts, Honolulu, Hawaii. Dr. Griffing wrote the preface to the catalogue for the Exhibition. Following its showing at Asia House, the Exhibition was shown at the Royal Ontario Museum, Toronto, Canada, and the Art Institute of Chicago, Chicago, Illinois.
  - Acoustiguide Script, undated (Box 46, Folder 400)
  - Catalogue: Annotated File Copy, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 401)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1967-1970 (Box 46, Folder 402)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 46, Folder 403)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript (1), 1967 (Box 46, Folder 404)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript (2), 1968 (Box 47, Folder 405)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript (3), undated (Box 47, Folder 406)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript (4), undated (Box 47, Folder 407)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Extra Copy, undated (Box 47, Folder 408)
  - Catalogue: Proofs: Griffing and Field Corrections, undated (Box 47, Folder 409)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, First: Griffing Corrections, undated (Box 47, Folder 410)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, Second: Griffing Corrections, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 411)
  - Condition Reports, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 412)
  - Correspondence: Domestic, 1964-1968, 1970-1972 (Box 48, Folder 413)
  - Correspondence: Robert P. Griffing, Jr., 1964-1969 (Box 48, Folder 414)
  - Daily Reports, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 415)
  - Guest Book, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 416)
  - Installation, 1967-1968 (Box 48, Folder 417)
  - Installation: Negatives, undated (Box 48, Folder 418)
  - Installation: Photos, Duplicates, undated (Box 48, Folder 419)
  - Insurance, 1967-1968 (Box 48, Folder 420)
  - "Korean Ceramics: An Art's Variety", Gregory Henderson, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 421)
  - Lectures, 1967-1968 (Box 49, Folder 422)
  - Loan Agreements A-J, 1967-1968 (Box 49, Folder 423)
  - Loan Agreements K-Z, 1967-1968 (Box 49, Folder 424)
  - Opening, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 425)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1967-1968 (Box 49, Folder 426)
  - Photos: Inferior, undated (Box 49, Folder 427)
  - Photos: Objects Not in Show, undated (Box 49, Folder 428)
  - Photos: Text Illustrations, Duplicates, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 429)
  - "Pottery Production in the Earliest Years of the Yi Period", Gregory Henderson, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 430)
  - Publicity, 1967-1969, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 431)
  - Slide Permission Letters, 1967-1968 (Box 50, Folder 432)
  - Travel of Exhibition: Chicago, 1967-1968 (Box 50, Folder 433)
  - Travel of Exhibition: General, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 434)
  - Travel of Exhibition: Toronto, 1967-1968 (Box 50, Folder 435)
- Ritual Vessels of Bronze Age China, Exhibited: 1968 October-December
  Professor Max Loehr, Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Professor of Oriental Art at Harvard University, Cambridge, Massachusetts, selected and catalogued the objects in the Exhibition.
  - Acoustiguide: Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 50, Folder 436)
  - Acoustiguide: Script, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 437)
  - Catalogue: Annotated File Copy, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 438)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1965, 1968-1969 (Box 50, Folder 439)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 50, Folder 440)
  - Catalogue: Letters and Notes Regarding Changes, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 441)
  - Catalogue: Loehr Manuscript with G. B. Washburn Corrections, undated (Box 51, Folder 442)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, undated (Box 51, Folder 443)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, undated (Box 51, Folder 444)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Original (1), undated (Box 51, Folder 445)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Original (2), undated (Box 51, Folder 446)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Typed, undated (Box 51, Folder 447)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Xerox Copy 2, undated (Box 52, Folder 448)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, Corrected (1), undated (Box 52, Folder 449)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, Corrected (2), undated (Box 52, Folder 450)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, Corrected (3), undated (Box 52, Folder 451)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, Corrected (4), undated (Box 52, Folder 452)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, Corrected (5), undated (Box 53, Folder 453)
  - Condition Reports, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 454)
  - Correspondence: Domestic, 1964-1965, 1967-1969 (Box 53, Folder 455)
  - Correspondence: Foreign, 1964, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 456)
  - Correspondence: Max Loehr, 1962-1968 (Box 53, Folder 457)
  - Daily Reports, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 458)
  - Guest Book, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 459)
  - Installation, 1963, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 460)
  - Insurance, 1967-1969 (Box 53, Folder 461)
  - Lectures, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 462)
  - Loan Agreements A-C, 1967-1969 (Box 54, Folder 463)
  - Loan Agreements D-N, 1963, 1967-1969 (Box 54, Folder 464)
  - Loan Agreements O-Z, 1967-1969, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 465)
  - Loan Refusals/Withdrawals, 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 466)
  - Opening, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 467)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1967-1969 (Box 55, Folder 468)
  - Photos: Inferior, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 469)
  - Photos: Objects Not in Show, 1967-1968 (Box 55, Folder 470)
  - Publicity, 1968-1970 (Box 55, Folder 471)
  - Slide Permission Letters, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 472)
  - Symposium, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 473)
- Chinese Art under the Mongols, Exhibited: 1969 January-March
  The Cleveland Museum of Art presented an Exhibition on the art of the Yüan Dynasty in China. The Exhibition contained 306 works assembled by Dr. Sherman E. Lee, the Museum's Director, and Wai-kam Ho, Curator of Oriental Art. Following its showing in Cleveland, the American loans, which comprised about one-third of the Exhibition, traveled to New York and were shown at the Asia House Gallery.
  - Acoustiguide Script, 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 474)
  - Catalogue: Annotated File Copy, undated (Box 56, Folder 475)
    EMPTY FOLDER
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 476)
  - Condition Reports, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 477)
  - Correspondence: Cleveland Museum of Art, 1964-1969 (Box 56, Folder 478)
  - Correspondence: General, 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 479)
  - Daily Reports, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 480)
  - Guest Book, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 481)
  - Installation, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 482)
  - Lectures, 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 483)
  - Loan Agreements, 1967-1969 (Box 56, Folder 484)
  - Opening, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 485)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 486)
  - Photos: Not in Show, undated (Box 57, Folder 487)
  - Publicity, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 488)
  - Yüan Art Symposium, Cleveland Museum of Art, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 489)
- The Art of Tibet, Exhibited: 1969 April-June
  The objects in the Exhibition were selected by Pratapaditya Pal, Keeper of the Indian Collections, Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, Massachusetts. The catalogue for the Exhibition was written by Dr. Pal and included an essay on Tibetan Ritual by Miss Eleanor Olson, Curator of Oriental Art at the Newark Museum, Newark, New Jersey. The Exhibition was shown at the Asia House Gallery and then traveled to the Smithsonian Institution in Washington, D.C. and The Seattle Museum, Washington.
  - Benefit: Auction, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 490)
  - Catalogue: Annotated File Copy, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 491)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 492)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 57, Folder 493)
  - Catalogue: First Galley Proof, Marked Set, undated (Box 57, Folder 494)
  - Catalogue: Introduction, undated (Box 58, Folder 495)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, undated (Box 58, Folder 496)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, undated (Box 58, Folder 497)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Original, undated (Box 58, Folder 498)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Original, undated (Box 58, Folder 499)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Original, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 500)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Original, undated (Box 59, Folder 501)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Original, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 502)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, Corrected, and Four Color Prints, undated (Box 59, Folder 503)
  - Catalogue: Second Proof, undated (Box 59, Folder 504)
  - Condition Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 60, Folder 505)
  - Correspondence: Domestic, 1963-1969 (Box 60, Folder 506)
  - Correspondence: Foreign, 1968-1969 (Box 60, Folder 507)
  - Correspondence: Indian Government, 1968-1969 (Box 60, Folder 508)
  - Correspondence: N. Jigme and R. L. Bartholomew, 1968-1969 (Box 60, Folder 509)
  - Correspondence: Pratapaditya Pal, 1964-1969 (Box 60, Folder 510)
  - Daily Reports, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 511)
  - Films, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 512)
  - Guest Book, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 513)
  - Installation, 1968-1969 (Box 61, Folder 514)
  - Installation: Photos, Duplicate, undated (Box 61, Folder 515)
  - Insurance, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 516)
  - Lectures, 1968-1969 (Box 61, Folder 517)
  - Loan Agreements A-G, 1968-1969 (Box 61, Folder 518)
  - Loan Agreements H-N, 1968-1969 (Box 61, Folder 519)
  - Loan Agreements R-Z, 1966, 1968-1970 (Box 62, Folder 520)
  - Loan Forms, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 521)
  - Loan Refusals and Withdrawals, 1968-1969 (Box 62, Folder 522)
  - "Mizue: A Monthly Review of the Fine Arts", No. 777, 1969/10 (Box 62, Folder 523)
  - Opening, 1968-1969 (Box 62, Folder 524)
  - Packing and Shipping: For Circulation, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 525)
  - Packing and Shipping: Incoming to Asia House Only, 1968-1969 (Box 62, Folder 526)
  - Packing and Shipping: Returns to Lenders, 1968-1970 (Box 63, Folder 527)
  - Photos: Inferior, undated (Box 63, Folder 528)
  - Photos: Not in Show, undated (Box 63, Folder 529)
  - Publicity, 1967-1971 (Box 64, Folder 530)
  - Slide Permission Letters, 1968, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 531)
  - Travel of Exhibition: General, 1968-1969 (Box 64, Folder 532)
  - Travel of Exhibition: Seattle, 1968-1970 (Box 64, Folder 533)
  - Travel of Exhibition: Smithsonian, 1968-1970 (Box 64, Folder 534)
  - Visit of the Dalai Lama, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 535)
- Ancient Cambodian Sculpture, Exhibited: 1969 October-December
  The objects in the Exhibition were selected by Sherman E. Lee, Director of The Cleveland Museum of Art, Cleveland, Ohio. Dr. Lee also authored the catalogue for the Exhibition.
  - Acoustiguide Script, undated (Box 64, Folder 536)
  - Catalogue: Annotated File Copy, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 537)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1969-1970 (Box 64, Folder 538)
  - Catalogue: Copy of Manuscript Corrected by Stanislaw Czuma, undated (Box 65, Folder 539)
  - Catalogue: Copy of Manuscript, Extra, Uncorrected, undated (Box 65, Folder 540)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 65, Folder 541)
  - Catalogue: First Proof, All Corrected, undated (Box 65, Folder 542)
  - Catalogue: First Proofs, Extra, Uncorrected, undated (Box 65, Folder 543)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript: Copy as Sent to Printer, undated (Box 65, Folder 544)
  - Catalogue: Marked for Otto Nelson for Slides, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 545)
  - Catalogue: Original Manuscript, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 546)
  - Catalogue: Page Proofs, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 547)
  - Catalogue: Proofs Corrected by Margaret F. Marcus, undated (Box 66, Folder 548)
  - Catalogue: Second Copy, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 549)